## Sarah Domson

 • Cape Coast, Central, Ghana
 ■ sarahdomson26@gmail.com
 ■ +233503584422

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sarah-domson-5749661a9/

#### **SUMMARY**

A nurse with 3 years of experience providing professional medical services for patients in the comfort of their own homes. Expert in understanding the needs of patients and their families, developing effective care plans and providing the highest level of care. Seeking a position to utilize my experience in providing high-quality healthcare services.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# HomeCare Nurse HomeMed Ghana

September 2022 - Present, Accra

- · Assisting patient with bathing, grooming and getting dressed.
- Handling household tasks like grocery shopping and laundry.
- Preparing and serving meals at the appropriate time.
- Administering oral and topical medication prescribed by the doctor.
- Check up on patient and monitor vital signs especially blood pressure.
- Taking patient to doctor's appointment and other activities.
- Providing information to family members regarding patient care.
- Documenting patient care and treatment.
- Providing company: chatting and sharing news.

#### Nurse Assistant

## JSI Research and Training Institute October 2020 - March 2022, Samartex Hospital, Samreboi

- Provide pre-test counselling information to people who wants to know their Human Immunodeficiency Virus (HIV) Status.
- · Counsel patients and their relatives and individuals on basic facts about HIV and AIDS.
- Conduct HIV testing services, interpret results and disclose results.
- Take vital signs of People Living with HIV(PLHIV) and enter details in the Antiretroviral Therapy (ART) register.
- · Collect blood samples from HIV exposed infants.
- Educate patients about HIV treatment plan.
- Take blood samples of patients who are due for viral load.
- Trace and bring back clients lost to follow up.
- Provide basic information about Antiretroviral drugs including side effects.
- · Inform patient on viral load test result.

#### Sales Supervisor Compu Mall Limited

June 2014 - December 2016, Cape Coast

- Understand customer needs and offer solutions and support.
- Organize and coordinate sales representatives' schedules.
- Research potential leads from business directories, web searches, or digital resources.
- · Recruit, hire, and train new sales representatives.
- · Receive and report on all sales leads.
- Supervise sales representatives and assistants.

- · Answer potential customer questions and follow-up call questions.
- · Work with sales team when closing sales.
- Track weekly, monthly, and quarterly performance and sales metrics.
- Meet all sales quotas and goals.
- · Assist sales representatives and team to meet and exceed goals.

#### STUDENT CLINICAL EXPERIENCE

#### Student Nurse - General Ward

Ghana Police Hospital • May 2019 - July 2019

- Dressing of wounds.
- · Serving of medications.
- Setting of tray for iv infusions.
- · Cleaning of wards.
- · Monitoring patient's progress and reporting to the charge nurse.
- · Collecting of samples for laboratory testing.

## Student Nurse - Emergency Unit

Greater Accra Regional Hospital, Accra · March 2018 - April 2018

- · Assisted in feeding of patient.
- · Serving of bed pans.
- · Bed making.
- · Assisted in serving of medication.
- · Setting of tray for procedures.
- · Assisted in passing NG-tube.
- · Documenting procedures.

### Student Nurse - Pediatric Emergency Unit

Komfo Anokye Teaching Hospital, Kumasi-Ghana · December 2017 - January 2018

- Checking of vital signs.
- Recording patient details.
- · Assisted in serving medications.
- · Documenting of procedures.
- Assisted in bed making.
- · Tidying up ward.

#### **EDUCATION**

## Certificate in Registered Nurse Assistant Clinical

Nursing and Midwifery Training School • Teshie, Ghana • 2019

#### **SKILLS**

**Technical Skills: Microsoft Office Suite** 

Soft Skills: Communication, Critical Thinking, Decision Making, Leadership, Coaching Mentoring